quotes on spongebob
1. “Firmly grasp it in your hand.”
2. “Ha ha ha ha, it’s a giraffe.”
3. “Once there was an ugly barnacle. He was so ugly that everyone died… the end.”
4. “Well, it’s no secret that the best thing about a secret is secretly telling someone your secret, thereby, secretly adding another secret to their secret collection of secret, secretly.”
5. “Do you smell it? That smell, the kind of smelly smell. A smelly smell that smells... smelly.”
6. “Is Mayonnaise an instrument?”
7. “F is for fire that burns down the whole town, U is for Uranium…bombs! N is for no survivors!”
8. “You don’t need a license to drive a sandwich.”
9. “The best time to wear a striped sweater…is all the time.”
10. “Can I be excused for the rest of my life?”

quotes on mark twain
1.”If you tell the truth, you don’t have to remember anything.” 
2.“The secret of getting ahead is getting started.”
3.“To succeed in life, you need two things: ignorance and confidence.”
4.“Courage is resistance to fear, mastery of fear – not absence of fear”
5.“The fear of death follows from the fear of life. A man who lives fully is prepared to die at any time.” 
6.“It’s not the size of the dog in the fight, it’s the size of the fight in the dog.” 
7.“Get your facts first, then you can distort them as you please.” 
8.“Kindness is the language which the deaf can hear and the blind can see.” 
9.“I have never let my schooling interfere with my education.” 
10.“You can’t depend on your eyes when your imagination is out of focus.” 

quotes on obama
1."You can’t let your failures define you. You have to let your failures teach you." 
2."Change will not come if we wait for some other person or some other time. We are the ones we've been waiting for. We are the change that we seek." 
3."When ignorant folks want to advertise their ignorance, you don't really have to do anything, you just let them talk." 
4."When times get tough, we don't give up. We get up." 
5."Change is never easy, but always possible."
6."Just because we have the best hammer does not mean that every problem is a nail." 
7."If somebody is different from you, that's not something you criticize, that's something that you appreciate." 
8."Where you are right now doesn't have to determine where you'll end up." 
9."Our destiny is not written for us, but by us." 
10."What makes you a man is not the ability to make a child, it's the courage to raise one." 

quotes on family
1. “A happy family is but an earlier heaven.”
2. “You leave home to seek your fortune and, when you get it, you go home and share it with your family.”
3. “Call it a clan, call it a network, call it a tribe, call it a family: Whatever you call it, whoever you are, you need one.”
4.“The family is one of nature’s masterpieces.” 
5.“Other things may change us, but we start and end with the family.” 
6.“Family is not an important thing, it’s everything.”
7.“Family means no one gets left behind or forgotten.” 
8.“The only rock I know that stays steady, the only institution I know that works, is the family.”
9.“Rejoice with your family in the beautiful land of life.”
10.“Families are like fudge – mostly sweet with a few nuts.”

quotes on mother
1.Mother’s love is peace. It need not be acquired, it need not be deserved.
2.God could not be everywhere, and therefore he made mothers.
3.We are born of love; Love is our mother.
4.A mother’s arms are made of tenderness and children sleep soundly in them.
5.It may be possible to gild pure gold, but who can make his mother more beautiful?
6.A child’s first teacher is its mother.
7.If evolution really works, how come mothers only have two hands?
8.Mothers are the only ones that think nothing is beyond their control when it comes to their children.
9.No matter your age, you always need your mom.
10.Home is where your mom is.

quotes on father
1.Behind every great daughter is a truly amazing dad.
2.“To her, the name of father was another name for love.”
3.“A father is a man who expects his son to be as good a man as he meant to be.”
4.“Of all the titles I’ve been privileged to have, ‘Dad’ has always been the best.”
5.“My father gave me the greatest gift anyone could give another person, he believed in me.”
6. “My father didn’t tell me how to live. He lived and let me watch him do it.” 
7.“There is nothing that moves a loving father's soul quite like his child's cry.” 
8.One father is more than a hundred schoolmasters.
9.Dad is and always will be my living, breathing superhero. 
10.It's an ongoing joy being a dad.

quotes on brother
1.“ Because brothers don't let each other wander in the dark alone.”
2.“ Sometimes being a brother is even better than being a superhero.
3.“ When brothers agree, no fortress is so strong as their common life.”
4.Because I have a brother I’ll always have a friend.
5.“What strange creatures brothers are!”
6.“Who needs superheroes when you have a brother.”
7.“A brother is a gift to the heart, a friend to the spirit.”
8.“I smile because you’re my brother. I laugh because there’s nothing you can do about it!”
9.“Being sister and brother means being there for each other.”
10.“Of all the toys I have to play, I’d choose my brothers.”

quotes on magic
1.❝Words and magic were in the beginning one and the same thing, and even today words retain much of their magical power.❞
2.Magic is believing in yourself, if you can do that, you can make anything happen.❞
3.❝Books are a uniquely portable magic.❞
4.❝If you see the magic in a fairy tale, you can face the future.❞
5.❝Magic is not a practice. It is a living, breathing web of energy that, with our permission, can encase our every action.❞
6.❝Art is magic delivered from the lie of being truth.❞
7.❝That's the thing with magic. You've got to know it's still here, all around us, or it just stays invisible for you.❞
8.❝Logic only gives man what he needs... Magic gives him what he wants.❞
9.❝Sometimes happiness is a blessing, but generally it is a conquest. Each day's magic moment helps.❞
10.❝A piece of writing is like a piece of magic. You create something out of nothing.❞

quotes on looks
1."Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work." 
2."If you have good thoughts they will shine out of your face like sunbeams and you will always look lovely."
3."Always look on the bright side of life." 
4."Who looks outside, dreams; who looks inside, awakes." 
5."Always look at what you have left. Never look at what you have lost."
6."What we see depends mainly on what we look for." 
7."Never bend your head. Always hold it high. Look the world straight in the eye." 
8."Sorrow looks back, Worry looks around, Faith looks up" 
9."Your vision will become clear only when you can look into your own heart.
10."Stay away from what might have been, and look at what can be." 

quotes on wind
1."And let the winds of the heavens dance between you." 
2."When you can’t change the direction of the wind — adjust your sails" 
3."Swift as the wind. Quiet as the forest. Conquer like the fire. Steady as the mountain" 
4."You find out the strength of a wind by trying to walk against it, not by lying down."
5."May the wind under your wings bear you where the sun sails and the moon walks." 
6."The pessimist complains about the wind; the optimist expects it to change; the realist adjusts the sails." 
7."The wind shows us how close to the edge we are." 
8."The older you get the stronger the wind gets and it's always in your face."
9."Rough winds do shake the darling buds of May." 
10."The winds with wonder whist, Smoothly the waters kisst." 

quotes on rain
1.Some people feel the rain. Others just get wet.
2.The best thing one can do when it's raining is to let it rain. 
3.The nicest thing about the rain is that it always stops. Eventually.     
4.Do not be angry with the rain; it simply does not know how to fall upwards.
5.A single gentle rain makes the grass many shades greener.
6.Rain showers my spirit and waters my soul.
7.I always like walking in the rain, so no one can see me crying.
8.A little rain each day will fill the rivers to overflowing. 
9.Rain does not fall on one roof alone.      
10.Whenever it rains you will think of her.

quotes on summer
1."It was June, and the world smelled of roses. The sunshine was like powdered gold over the grassy hillside."
2."Everything good, everything magical happens between the months of June and August."
3."August rain: the best of the summer gone, and the new fall not yet born. The odd uneven time."
4."Life, now, was unfolding before me, constantly and visibly, like the flowers of summer that drop fanlike petals on eternal soil."
5."Green was the silence, wet was the light,
6."If it could only be like this always – always summer, always alone, the fruit always ripe and Aloysius in a good temper..."
7."The morning heat had already soaked through the walls, rising up from the floor like a ghost of summers past."
8."I have only to break into the tightness of a strawberry, and I see summer – its dust and lowering skies."
9."I felt like summer had taken over me."
10."Sweet, sweet burn of sun and summer wind, and you my friend, my new fun thing, my summer fling." 

quotes on flowers
1.After women, flowers are the most lovely thing God has given the world.
2.Flowers are restful to look at. They have neither emotions nor conflicts.     
3.To me, flowers are happiness. 
4.I'd rather have roses on my table than diamonds on my neck.
5.Flowers seem intended for the solace of ordinary humanity.
6.Every flower is a soul blossoming in nature.
7.Flowers are words which even a babe may understand.
8.Where flowers bloom so does hope.
9.Flowers are love's truest language.
10.A flower blossoms for its own joy.

quotes on happy
1.We don’t laugh because we’re happy – we’re happy because we laugh.
2.Don’t cry because it’s over, smile because it happened.
3.Now and then it’s good to pause in our pursuit of happiness and just be happy.
4.Doing what you like is freedom. Liking what you do is happiness. 
5.Life is 10 percent what happens to you and 90 percent how you respond to it.
6.True happiness arises, in the first place, from the enjoyment of one’s self.
7.Time you enjoy wasting is not wasted time.
8.Folks are usually about as happy as they make their minds up to be.
9.Happiness? That’s nothing more than health and a poor memory. 
10.People don’t notice whether it’s winter or summer when they’re happy.

quotes on cake
1.Cakes have such a terrible habit of turning out bad just when you especially want them to be good. 
2.My idea of baking is buying a ready make cake mix and throwing in an egg.
3.Take the broken pieces of your life, bake a master cake out of it. 
4.Every birthday, every celebration ends with something sweet, a cake, and people remember. 
5.Happiness is like a cake: have too much of it and you get sick of it.     
6.Life is a cake and love is the icing on top of it.
7.Where there is cake, there is hope. And there is always cake.
8.If I was made of cake i'd eat myself before somebody else could.
9.Cakes are healthy too, you just need to eat a small slice.
10.A party without cake is really just a meeting.
   
quotes on god
1.“God will never give you anything you can’t handle, so don’t stress.”
2.“Yesterday is history, tomorrow is a mystery, today is God’s gift, that’s why we call it the present.”
3.“Every man’s life is a fairy tale written by God’s fingers.”
4.“Love God and He will enable you to love others even when they disappoint you.”
5.“Faith is about trusting God when you have unanswered questions.”
6.“Never be afraid to trust an unknown future to a known God.”
7.“I believe that whatever comes at a particular time is a blessing from God.”
8.“Pray, and let God worry.” 
9.“When the solution is simple, God is answering.” 
10.“If you suffer, thank God! It is a sure sign that you are alive.”

quotes on royal
1.Be Royal in your Own Fashion
2. Act like a King to be treated lik one.
3."In the past, people were born royal. Nowadays, royalty comes from what you do." 
4."The royal road to a man's heart is to talk to him about the things he treasures most." 
5."There's nothing so kingly as kindness,And nothing so royal as truth."
6."There is only one royal road for the spiritual journey...Love" 
7."Royalty is completely different than celebrity. Royalty has a magic all on its own." 
8."They are not royal. They just happen to have me as their aunt." 
9.“You are enough to drive a saint to madness or a king to his knees.”
10.“Oh honey, someday a real man is going to make you see stars and you won't even be looking at the sky." 

quotes on glitter
1.“All that is gold does not glitter,Not all those who wander are lost.” 
2.“Broken glass. It's just like glitter, isn't it?” 
3.“Glitter is the herpes of craft supplies.” 
4.“Magic was not in glitter and sparks. Real magic didn't need to be.”
5.“She glitters like she walked out of a Klimt painting” 
6."she leaves a little glitter where ever she goes."
7."Some girls are just born with glitter in their veins." 
8."All that glitters is not gold." 
9."There’s a massive glitter ball in my head and it has never stopped turning" 
10."I have a magpie mind. I like anything that glitters." 

quotes on stars
1.The stars are the land-marks of the universe.
2.There wouldn't be a sky full of stars if we were all meant to wish on the same one.
3.It is not in the stars to hold our destiny but in ourselves.  
4.The stars are the jewels of the night.
5.When it is darkest, men see the stars. 
6.God's promises are like the stars; the darker the night the brighter they shine.
7.The stars are the street lights of eternity. 
8.Never judge the moon by gazing the stars.     
9.Keep your eyes on the stars, and your feet on the ground
10.The sky is filled with stars, invisible by day.  

quotes on moon
1.“Everyone is a moon, and has a dark side which he never shows to anybody.” 
2.“Yours is the light by which my spirit's born: - you are my sun, my moon, and all my stars.” 
3.“Don't tell me the moon is shining; show me the glint of light on broken glass.” 
4.“We ran as if to meet the moon.” 
5."You have been mooned."
6. "My soul is in the sky." 
7."Just like the moon, I go through phases." 
8."I love you to the moon and back."
9."Shoot for the moon, darling." 
10."She and the moon could always be found playing in the darkness." 
